KARAN JADAV



Contact

Address:

Shivam, Soni talavadi, Jerambhai no chowk, Dhrangadhra, 363310 **Phone:**

6353351911

Email:

karanjadav313@gmail.com

COURSE	%OF MARKS
SSC	73
HSC	75
B.E CGPA	7.52

Summary

Engineer focused on sustainable design. Highly effective at working with teams of designers and makers to accomplish projects on-time and according to cost constraint.

Skill Highlights

- Computer Aided Designing
- Additive Manufacturing
- Product Designing
- Research and Design activities

Experience

(1) Design And Prototype Engineer -04/2022 to 08/2022

Company: Vama Communications

Being at VAMA Communications I have worked on different projects where I applied my CAD and 3D Printing skills. It drove me to learn different set of skill of integrating different electrical parts in CAD modelling and 3D Printing.

3D CAD: Designing, repairing, modifying 3D CAD data Maintenance: Operating, repairing and testing 3D printers Maintained production line of 3D printed projects for 5 printers.

(2) Production Engineer: 04/2023 to continue

Company: TATA GOTION GREEN ENERGY SOLUTION PVT.LTD

Excellent problem-solving and extensive knowledge of the manufacturing process and the development of equipment and production lines. Outstanding design and conceputal skills with the motivational abilities to lead a team. Dedicated to producing the best work with Following safety measures.

Internship

DCW.LTD COMPANY - 01/2022 to 03/2022

I have done my internship in DCW.LTD COMPANY at dhrangadhra.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering: Mechanical Engineering- 2018-2022

LJ Institute Of Engineering And Technology, Ahmedabad